Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series VII: Tours
  - 2000-01 Hotel Rooms (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Travel Agents (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Touring Inquiries (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Long Beach Tour (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 1997/98 Hotel Needs (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Tour - Mills College (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Sample Touring Contracts/Advances (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1994-1994 Touring (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Artist transport (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Long Beach (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Brasil Tour 2001 materials (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Touring possibilities resources (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Canada (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - China (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Australia Council (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - April 1991 Soviet (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Orchestra touring costs (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Lenita Johnson and Sonoma County AFM (American Fed. of Musicians) organizations (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Oregon Touring (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Chinese-American Cultural Bridge Center (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Jay Hoffman (Beach/Polk Tour) (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Indiana University of Penn. Music Festival 2000 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - 1994 Northern California Tour materials (Part I) (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - 1994 Northern California Tour materials (Part II) (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - WP performances, 1994-1998 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Official Invitation to China Tour, 1994 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Greece Tour, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 11)
- Series VIII: Marketing
  Development
  This includes marketing materials; press releases; press packets; advertisers and advertising campaigns; donor lists; marketing and audience surveys; direct mail efforts and graphic design artists and materials.
  - Speaking Engagements 1991/92 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 2/9/1991 Comet/LaBarbara (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 1991-92 Subscription Campaign (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 1992 St. Mary's Alum (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - 1992-93 Program and Publication Newsletters (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 1993-94 Publications and Programs Newsletters (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 1997-98 Season Programs (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Business Women 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bay Times (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Culture Index/Online Ticketing (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Development Committee (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Flyer Mailing (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Lists of Area Arts Organizations (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Concert Flyering List (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Eureka/Theater (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Gaurdian (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Human Intervention (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Listings (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Mamma Bears (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Promotional Items (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Misc. WP Concert/Event Programs (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper articles (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Outreach/Mailing Lists (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Yerba Buena Gardens (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 1994-95 Community Outreach/Ticket donations (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Womens Philharmonic (TWP) Quote Sheet (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - 1999 Subscription Mailings (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Education/outreach 2001-02 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Communications/Marketing (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Educ. Outreach (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Listings (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bulk Mail (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Marketing 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 1991-92 Season Marketing Materials (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 1993-94 Ads (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1993-94 Marketing (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 1994-95 Marketing (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1994-95 Season ads (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 1994/95 Ad Sales (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 1995-96 Marketing (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Marketing 1996-97 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1996/97 Telemarketing (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - 1997/98 Season Telemarketing (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Critical response Marketing 99-2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Festival Marketing (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Flyers + Ads (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - KDFC (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - KDFC (radio station) (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - KDFC (radio station) Contract (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - KKHI Radio Spots (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - To: Marketing Chair (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Marketing Committee (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Committee (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Marketing/Communications (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Materials (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Ads (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Partners (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Program Ad Specs 4/3/1999 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Recording Ad (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Telemarketing (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Telemarketing Campaign (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1992-93 Advertisers (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1991-92 Advertisers (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1992-93 Ad Rate Mailing (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ads 92-93 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - 1991-92 Ads (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - 1992 Brochure (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ad payables (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Advertising (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Direct Mail (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Yellow Pages Ad (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Direct Mail 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Celebrating Women in Music (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Sept 30 2000 Press Release (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - GMC-Trojans and Amazons (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - May 26, 2000 Concert Release (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Oct 16 Press Release (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Previews/Promo (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Feb 26, 2000 Press Release (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Cindi Hubbard Press Release (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 5/7/1999 JoAnn Falletta Resigns Press Release (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 5/3/1999 Music in the Making (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 4/3/99 Concert Long Press release (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - 4/3/91 Concert Press Release (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - 2000-2001 Concert Season Announcemnet (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - 4/7/1999 Long Release Concert (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 9/14/98 Concert Press Release (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - 10/15/98 Nov. Concert Press (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Press Release Nat'l Women Conductors Initiative (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - May 2 1998 Press Release (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - 3/7/98 Brass with Class PSAs and Press Release (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - 5/2/98 U.S. and West Coast Premier Highlight Concert (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - 12/18 p.r. 1/23/99 Concert (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - 2/7/98 Concert Press Release (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - 7/31/98 Reading Session Press Release (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Press Release Symph/Rec session 11/15-16 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Press Release: ASCAP 5/98 Award/Apo (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 11/15/1997 Public Service Announcements (PSAs) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1997-98 Season Press Release (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "A Few Good Women" auction items (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - 3/1/1997 Press Release (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 5/20/1997 Apo Hsu at A.D. Press Release (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - 5/5/1997 PR for Chen Yi CD (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 3/29/1997 PR (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 1/25/1997 Dela Martinez Press Release (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - 9/1996 Music in the Making PR (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - 8/27/1996 Scharffenberger event PR (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - 1996/97 15th Anniversary Season PR (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - WP Meets Goal Press Release 1/26/1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Paid Advertising 96-97 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Press Conference 6/17/98 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Press Kit Enclosures (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Marketing (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Chen Yi CD Marketing (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - KEST Radio (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - PR 1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - WP's 2nd Decade 1992 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - postard for 1/25/1997 Concert (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Ad Exchange (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - PR 1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Advertising 1998-99 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Thank You Letters to volunters and donors 1999 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - VIP Invitation Letter from Apo Hsu (2000) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases 1997-1999 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Packets for Press Kits 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Sample Donor Request Letters November 1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Restaurant and Parking Guide 1999 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Ad Specs 1999/2000 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Major Donor List 1999 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Major Donor Information Wrap Up 1999 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - 1999-2000 Fundraising (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - January 1996 Strategic plan (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - 1995 Strategic Planning, Notes and Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Women's Philharmonic Strategic Planning 1995 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - 1999 Gala Telemarketing Script and phone numbers (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - 92-93 minisub (telemarketing campaign) (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Major Donor 2003 Calls/Scripts (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Major Donor Campaign FY01 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Fall 2002 Solicitation (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Women's Philharmonic Farewell 2004/Misc (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Adventures in Music: SF Symphony (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - April 3, 1999 Concert marketing (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Jan. 23, 1999 Concert marketing (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - 1998-1999 Season brochure materials (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - 1998-1999 Season marketing (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Feb. 2, 1997 Marketing ideas and leads notes (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - 1998-1999 Paid Advertising notes/materials (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Newsletters/Brocuhures: other organizations (2003) (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - San Jose Mercury News photo order request (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - 1999 Marketing (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - 1998-1999 Program ad sales (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - 1997-1998 Program advertising (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - 1996-1997 Program ads. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Concert Flyers (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Misc. WP Brouchures (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Brochure (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Summer 2000 KWMR Victor Honig (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Direct mail materials 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Direct mail materials 1997-1998 con't (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Direct mail materials con't 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 1997-1999 Marketing + subscription materials (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - 1997-1999 Marketing + Subscription materials continued (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - 1997-1999 Marketing + subscription materials con't. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi Project Marketing materials (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - October 3, 1998 "A Few Good Women" Auction/Fundraiser materials (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Chen Yi June 1996 Media (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Chen Yi June 1996 Marketing (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi Project recording materials (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi Project: production notes (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi Program materials (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Publicity: misc. resources (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Florence Price Cd Release (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Program Notes mailing Feb. 26, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Direct mailing/phone materials 2001 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - 1997 Marketing Pieces (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - 1997 - 1998 Subscription Renewal (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 1994-95 Subscription Renewal (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Mail List, Letter + Script (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Early Subscriber Mailing 1996 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - 1991/92 Subscribe/Renew Letters (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - June 1996 Concert Attendees (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Subscription Renewal Reminder (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Video production materials (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Record Stores Mailing 1/17/1997 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Mini Subscription Offer Feb. 1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Postcard Mailing for Concert 3/29/97 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Postcard Mailing for Concert 3/1/97 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - 1/25/1997 Prog. Note Mailing (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Audience Survey Spring 1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Harvard/Radcliff Alums (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Mischell Re-broadcasts (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mailing List (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Sample Season Brochures (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 1993-94 Season General information (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Subscription Info (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Direct mail planning: 1995-1998 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Sample direct mail letters 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Mailing list purchase materials 1996 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Direct mail analysis (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Solicitation letter enclosures (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - direct mail: June 1998 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Direct mail--general 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Mailing list rental income 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - "A Few Good women" confirmed auction items (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Nov. 5, 1998 Major Donor Dinner (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Major donor pledges 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Washington, D.C. donor members list (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - L.A. donor member list (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - New York City donor member (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - New York/Washington D.C. membership meetings October 1996 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Marketing: Season brouchures 1998-1999 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Season materials 1997-1998 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Season brochures 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Marketing materials 1995-1996 season (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - 1994-1995 season marketing materials (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Season marketing materials 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Season marketing materials 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Programs 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Season marketing 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - 1989-1990 season marketing (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Season marketing materials 1988-1989 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Marketing materials 1987-1988 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - 1986-1987 Season marketing materials (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - 1985-1986 season marketing (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - May 2, 1998 marketing (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - March 7, 1998 marketing (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - February 7, 1998 marketing (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - November 15, 1997 marketing (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - 1997-1998 paid advertising (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Advertising 1995 concert programs (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - 1997-1998 marketing (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Designers (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - H + S Design (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Rebecca Martinez Design (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Miriam Lewis Graphic Design (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Art (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Club (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 1993 Classical Public Radio Sacramento (CPRS) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Women's Phil Facts (for marketing) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - 1998 KKHI Radio: concert broadcasts (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - 1994-1995 Marketing schedule (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Mailing List vendor materials (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Sample Asks; Sample Annual Reports (1998) (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Marketing communication plan April 1998 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Acquisition Campaign financing 1998 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - "Performance Today" and NPR radio materials (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Sponsor options 1997 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Final membership attempt mailing August 1997 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Apo Hsu Appeal Letter May 16, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - May 1997 Special Appeal Letter and NEA Challenge materials (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - October 1997 Audience survey responses (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Spring 1997 Direct mail schedule (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Membership Mailing #1: Feb. 3, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Membership reminder mailing #2 March 24, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Membership reminder mailing #3 June 2, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Sustainers Circle Membership materials (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Recording donation appeal April 1996 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Boulanger-themed Donation Appeal April 1996 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - 1996 Holiday Donations Appeal (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - New Members Mailing materials 1996 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - 1996 Direct Mail Campaign (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - November 1995 Membership Campaign materials (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Membership and newsletter materials, December 1995 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - House Appeal materials, September 1995 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Membership mailing materials, February 1996 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Women's Philharmonic Special Events Assessment tool, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Audience survey, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Ticket donations (FY 2001) (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Donor appeal (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Conductor's Project (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - In-House Appeal, June 1998 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Monday reports and general correspondence, 12/1998 - 4/1999 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Cold mail, January 1999 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Renewal, 3/1999 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Coding Issues, 1999 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - House Appeal, 4/1999 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - House Appeal paperwork, 7/1998-10/1998 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - House Appeal reports, 1999 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Benjamin & Co. reports, 12/1998 - 3/1999 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Benjamin & Co. (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Driscoll / Horton (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters - to approach for member acquist/Merch. (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Renewal 2/99 with survey (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - 1998-1999 Season Brochure (non WP) (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Items for e-mail broadcasts (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Subscription (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Youth initiative, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Comp tickets for youth organizations (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Subscription refunds, 2001/2002 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Marketing - letters, 1998 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Misc. advertisers, 2003 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Marketing / PR (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Driscoll / Horton Advertising agreement and materials, 2004 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Brochure mailing, 1999/2000 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Graphic designers (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Concert Marketing, October 16, 1999 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Marketing materials: March 25, 2000 concert (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Joanne Polk: Media contacts (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Cindy Cox: marketing and correspondence (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Sara Jobin: May 26, 2000 concert (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Kendra Colton: May 26, 2000 concert (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - "A Few Good Woman" materials (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Subscriber (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Subscription campaign, 2000-2001 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Ticket subscribers, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Audience survey, 1998 (part I) (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Audience survey, 1998 (part II) (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Direct Mail Appeal Letters materials, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Major Donors appeal letters and materials, 2001 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Postcards: Direct Mail Cost and postage (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - LOGOS for promotion/advertising Development "must-haves" (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Inkworks: quotes and orders (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Marketing: publicity / promo (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Marketing notes and materials (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Marketing: ticket sales (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Small donor sampling, 1995 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Apo - Outreach / Public Speaking Ideas (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Frontline Telephone Marketing agreement materials (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Gail Taras: Taras Design, 1997/1998 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Concert Postcards (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Ads (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Program Ads: ER concert (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Brand Development (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Audience survey, 9/1991 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Audience survey, 10/1997 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Audience survey, 1999-2000 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Audience survey, 5/1999 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Audience survey, 5/2/1998 (Box 165, Folder 10)
- Series IX: Composer Initiatives/Resources
  Composer Initiatives
  This includes information about the New Music Reading Sessions (NMRS), the American Women Masters Series (AWMS), the National Womens Composer Resource Center (NWCRC) a "Composing a Career" Symposium and the Lili Boulanger Award for composition. A list of composers whose work was selected for performance at the New Music Reading Sessions and those whose work was commissioned is also included.
  - Miscellaneous Composers Resources
    - American Composers Orchestra (ACO) Correspondence and newsletters (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - American Women Composers Midwest, Inc. (AWC) (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Anne Grey: "Popular guide to women in classical music" (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Ars Femina (chamber ensemble) (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Budget 1991-1993 Emerging Composers (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Chromatica-Selma Epstein (pianist/scholar) (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Composers 1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Composers Guild (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Composer/Programs (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Women's music organizations (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - New York Women composers (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Renaissance women composers (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Women Composers + Conductors: dictionary draft (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Women Composers: Misc. Materials (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Women in music bibliography (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Womens music organizations + resources (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Women composers organizations (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Judy Gerst Woman Composer Request 9/2000 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Non-Women's Philharmonic Calls for Scores, Awards, etc (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - 2003 Festival of Women Composers: contract + correspondence (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - 1996 Performing committments: compositions (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Submission Requests (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Screening forms (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - National Women Conductors Initiative (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Resource Center Assessment (Box 151, Folder 27)
  - Composing a Career Symposium
    Composing a Career
    This file contains materials related to this symposium organized by the Women's Philharmonic at the New School in New York City in 1999. Designed to bring women composers together in order to share information on how to publish their compositions it also afforded selected female composers the opportunity to hear their work performed at the symposium during a "reading session."
    - Composing A Career symposium 11/1997 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Mills College Symposium (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Symposium Evaluations (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Symposium-print bio (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Brochure--symposium (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Symposium 11/1997--"Debrief" (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Symposium 11/1997 Program/Registration (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Symposium 11/1997 handbook (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Symposium schedule and timeline Nov. 1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Registration & returned confirmation (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Symposium Registration (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Mills College Symposium (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Symposium-hotel/operations (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Symposium mail lists (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Symposium (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Panelists (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Mills conference center (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Symposium-organization (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - "Composing a Career" Brochure (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Symposium--budget and timeline (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Compsoer Symposium 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Symposium Evaluations (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Interest in "Composing a Career" (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Panelist Bios (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Symposium Handbook (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Symposium Fall 1997 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Fran Richard (ASCAP Vice President/composing a career seminar) (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Pauline Oliveros (Composer/Mills Faculty) (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - David Harrington (KRONOS Quartet founder/Mills Faculty) (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - 1999-2000 Composer symposium (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - 2002 Composer symposium registration materials (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Composer Symposium materials (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Composing a Career Symposium evaluations materials (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - 2002 Composer symposium materials (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - 2002 Composer symposium notes (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - 1999 Composing a Career Attendee list (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Symposium attendee packet materials (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Resource handbook for composing a career (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Composing a Career and Music in the Making materials (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Composer Symposium print bids (Box 120, Folder 5)